Why is he here?
Is he going to capture me
for a sacrifice again?
Little one, I'm here to pick you up.
P-P-Pick me up?
Exactly.
Wait a minute.
Shouldn't you ask for my permission
before taking me away?
The High Priest of the Demonic Cult
sneaking into my Qi Residence
just to fight me for a woman?
So she is a woman.
No wonder she's so pretty.
That makes me even more interested in her.
Let's have a duel.
The winner gets her.
You overestimate yourself.
I don't belong to anyone!
Such a commotion.
Is Mister going to be okay?
I can't believe I'm worrying
about that jerk.
M-Mister,
why are you suddenly here?
Where is Hong?
I drove him away.
As for you,
you promised to stay.
Why did you run away again?
And
in such ugly men's clothes, too.
It seems I need to punish you properly.
M-Mister...
Master Yan.
No,
Yanmo.
You must be suffering too.
Your internal organs are damaged.
Enjoy the pain of your body
being corroded.
But your woman
is indeed quite interesting.
A woman who can make Yanmo so nervous.
No wonder she is the chosen one
from heaven.
My Lady, are you still worrying
about the Sect Leader?
Commander Ye,
stop calling me My Lady.
Why?
Don't you like the Sect Leader?
It's him who doesn't like me.
Back at the Black Wind Stronghold,
he totally wanted me dead.
That's not true.
The Sect Leader just had
his own difficulties.
When you were kidnapped,
he was the most anxious one.
Later, when you were poisoned,
he stayed by your side
for three whole days and nights.
W-What?
Are you saying
that Mister likes me?
Master Yan is here.
I'm really sorry about
what happened last time.
I have already dealt with that spy.
I am Bai Ze.
A pleasure to meet you.
Cut the crap.
Yungong Pavilion claims
to know everything.
I asked you to investigate a woman,
so why is there still no news?
Within the Five Realms,
Yungong Pavilion knows everything.
But beyond the Five Realms,
it's hard to say.
The person you want to investigate
is no ordinary human.
All I can say is,
whoever gets Akong,
gets the world.
Oh,
let's talk this out nicely.
Bastard!
Do you know
how much danger
those words will bring her?
I warn you.
If you dare leak the news,
I will end you.
Fine, fine.
Remember my words.
Whether the news spreads
depends on my mood.
Besides, I want that woman for myself too.
Mr. Bai, a lady is asking to see you.
Let her in.
The butler said he is here.
I must ask him to clarify
what Commander Ye said last night.
Lady Akong,
you were looking for me?
You know me?
Not only do I know you,
but I also know you are here for
Young Master Yan of the Qi Manor.
Follow me.
By the way, this is for you.
What is this?
A mirror.
It might help in times of danger.
Consider it an apology
for the incident at Yungong Pavilion.
How can a mirror help?
But it is quite pretty.